Guide to the Yasser Alwan Collection 1890-1970 AD.MC.002
AbuDhabi
- Series II: Egypt, 1895-1971 (Box 1-7)
  - Four children pose with various props against a painted backdrop. 8.6 x 13.6 cm, Undated; Studio M. Khaled (Box 3, Folder 21)
    Books; Children; Egypt; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Statues; Studio Photography
  - Two men in miltary uniform. 12.0 x 8.8 cm, 29 July 1938; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 21)
    Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Greek Writing; Men; Military / Soldiers; Photographic Prints; Uniforms
  - A seated woman with two girls wearing black bows in their hair 13.7 x 8.7 cm, Undated; Studio Photo Moderne, Alexandria, Egypt (Box 3, Folder 21)
    Alexandria, Egypt; Armenian Writing; Family Portraits; Fashion Accessories; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
  - Two men in suits and a woman in a bathing suit pose on a boat. 8.9 x 13.8 cm, 3 July 1931; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 21)
    Bathing Suits / Swimsuits; Beaches; Boats; Cesme, Izmir, Turkey; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Seas; Turkish Writing; Women
  - Two seated women with a standing man in a sailor's uniform. 13.7 x 8.6 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 21)
    Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Makeup; Men; Military / Soldiers; Navy; Photographic Prints; Uniforms; Women
  - Two men in suits. 13.6 x 8.6 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Sedat Izmir, Hukumet Caddesi (Turkey) (Box 3, Folder 22)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Handkerchief; Izmir, Turkey; Men; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Suits
  - Two women seated on a bench. 13.9 x 8.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 22)
    Clocks & Watches; Egypt; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Jewellery; Makeup; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
  - A group of three men and two women swimming in a pool. 9.4 x 14.3 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 22)
    Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Swimming; Swimming Pools; Women
  - A woman seated in a wicker chair outdoors in front of a stone building. 13.9 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 22)
    Egypt; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Women
  - A negative image of four women sitting at a cafe. 9.1 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 22)
    Bars; Drinking; Egypt; Fur Garments; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Negative Images; Photographic Prints; Restaurants; Women
  - A woman wearing a dark outfit with a white collar and white gloves. 13.9 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 22)
    Egypt; Fashion Accessories; Gelatin Silver Prints; Gloves; Head Covers; Individual Portraits; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
  - A multi-generational group pose in front of a building. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 22)
    Architecture; Buildings; Children; Clocks & Watches; Egypt; Fezes / Tarbouches; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Women
  - A couple standing in doorway, a man wearing a tarbouche and glasses holds a woman's face, possibly from a film. 13.9 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 22)
    Egypt; Eye Glasses & Sunglasses; Fezes / Tarbouches; Film Stills; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Women
  - A hand-painted portrait of a woman wearing a blue jacket. 13.3 x 8.4 cm, Undated; Studio Photo London, 26 Boulevard Abbas, Heliopolis (Cairo, Egypt) (Box 3, Folder 22)
    Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Hand-colored Photographs / Hand-tinting; Individual Portraits; Jewellery; Makeup; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
  - A woman wearing an outfit with a lace collar, looking off camera. 13.5 x 8.6 cm, Undated; Studio Photo Oases, Heliopolis (Cairo, Egypt) (Box 3, Folder 22)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Heliopolis, Cairo, Egypt; Individual Portraits; Jewellery; Makeup; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
  - A young man in a suit with a book on his lap. M. Sheredan. 13.5 x 8.6 cm, Undated; Heyworth's Studios, St. Annes on Sea, England; Jenkins, C. (Box 3, Folder 23)
    Books; England; English Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Lancashire, England; Men; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
  - A studio portrait of a couple, the woman wears a dress with a patterned collar. 13.7 x 8.6 cm, Undated; Studio Badr (Egypt) (Box 3, Folder 23)
    Couples; Egypt; Fezes / Tarbouches; Gelatin Silver Prints; Jewellery; Makeup; Men; Mustaches; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
  - Women and children gathered around a fountain, filling a jug with water. 14.0 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 23)
    Babies; Children; Egypt; Fountains; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Women
  - A group sitting in a boat (linked ref655). 8.7 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 23)
    Boats; Children; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Nile River; Photographic Prints; Women
  - Two women from ref654 standing on the stairs of a porch in front of a house. 13.9 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 23)
    Architecture; Buildings; Family; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Unknown Locations; Women
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - Two men in three piece suits and hats, leaning on a car on a street. 8.4 x 6.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 23)
    Cars; Cigarettes; Eye Glasses & Sunglasses; Gelatin Silver Prints; Germany; Hats; Men; Photographic Prints; Smoking; Streets; Trees
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - A woman sitting in the driver's seat of a convertible car. 6.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 23)
    Cars; Gelatin Silver Prints; Germany; Photographic Prints; Streets; Trees; Women
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - Three women and one man standing on the sidewalk in front of a Dodge (car). 6.1 x 8.6 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 23)
    Cars; Eye Glasses & Sunglasses; Gelatin Silver Prints; Germany; Hats; Men; Photographic Prints; Streets; Women
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - A woman wearing a light dress seated at an outdoor cafe near a lake. 6.4 x 8.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 23)
    Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Germany; Jewellery; Lakes; Makeup; Photographic Prints; Restaurants; Women
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - A young girl standing on a dirt path with a walking stick wearing winter clothes. 6.2 x 6.0 cm, November 1937; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 23)
    Budapest, Hungary; Children; Coats; Countryside / Rural; English Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Germany; Girls; Photographic Prints
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - A young woman wearing a white bathing suit sitting on the beach (same woman as ref662). 9.0 x 6.0 cm, Undated; Photo-Kino Fritz, Berlin, CH-2 (Germany) (Box 3, Folder 24)
    Bathing Suits / Swimsuits; Beaches; Gelatin Silver Prints; Germany; Makeup; Photographic Prints; Women
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - A woman sitting on the beach in a white bathing suit (same woman as ref661). 9.0 x 6.0 cm, Undated; Photo-Kino Fritz, Berlin, CH-2 (Germany) (Box 3, Folder 24)
    Bathing Suits / Swimsuits; Beaches; Berlin, Germany; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - A woman wearing a fur trimmed coat standing in front of a car (same location as ref666). 9.0 x 6.0 cm, Undated; Photo-Kino Fritz, Berlin, CH-2 (Germany) (Box 3, Folder 24)
    Berlin, Germany; Buildings; Cars; Coats; Countryside / Rural; Fur Garments; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - The 1936 Olympics with Hitler. 6.1 x 8.9cm, August 1936; Photo-Kino Fritz, Berlin, CH-2 (Germany) (Box 3, Folder 24)
    Berlin, Germany; Flags; Gelatin Silver Prints; Hitler, Adolf; Military / Soldiers; Nazis; Olympic Games; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - Two men standing on a balcony (same location as ref669). 8.6 x 6.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 24)
    Balcony / Terrace; Eye Glasses & Sunglasses; Gelatin Silver Prints; Germany; Houses; Men; Photographic Prints; Suits
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - Hussein Rushdy Beg standing in front a car (same location as ref663). 9.0 x 5.9 cm, Undated; Photo-Kino Fritz, Berlin, CH-2 (Germany) (Box 3, Folder 24)
    Berlin, Germany; Buildings; Cars; Countryside / Rural; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Suits
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - A woman wearing a patterned swimsuit. 6.0 x 6.2 cm, Undated; Photo-Kino Fritz, Berlin, CH-2 (Germany) (Box 3, Folder 24)
    Bathing Suits / Swimsuits; Berlin, Germany; Cigarettes; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Smoking; Studio Photography; Women
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - A woman wearing a pencil skirt suit standing in front of a convertible (same location as ref670). 9.0 x 6.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 24)
    Architecture; Buildings; Cars; Countryside / Rural; Flags; Gelatin Silver Prints; Germany; Photographic Prints; Suits; Women
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - Hussein Rushdy Beg (right) with another man on a balcony (same location as 665). 6.0 x 8.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 24)
    Eye Glasses & Sunglasses; Gelatin Silver Prints; Germany; Houses; Men; Photographic Prints; Suits
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - Hussein Rushdy Beg standing with his arms behind his back in front of a convertible (same location as ref668). 6.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 24)
    Architecture; Buildings; Cars; Flags; Gelatin Silver Prints; Germany; Houses; Men; Photographic Prints; Suits
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - Hussein Rushdy Beg standing in a garden in a robe and bathing suit. 6.0 x 6.2 cm, Undated; Photo-Kino Fritz, Berlin, CH-2 (Germany) (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Bathing Suits / Swimsuits; Berlin, Germany; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Robes; Studio Photography
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - A woman standing in a white dress and hat at a race track. 6.0 x 6.2 cm, Undated; Photo-Kino Fritz, Berlin, CH-2 (Germany) (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Berlin, Germany; Gelatin Silver Prints; Hats; Horse Racing; Horses; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - Hussein Rushdy Beg and a woman in a dark dress standing in front of a large estate. 6.0 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Photo-Kino Fritz, Berlin, CH-2 (Germany) (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Architecture; Berlin, Germany; Buildings; Couples; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - A woman wearing a fur-trimmed coat standing on a tree-lined road. 9.0 x 6.0 cm, Undated; Photo-Kino Fritz, Berlin, CH-2 (Germany) (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Berlin, Germany; Coats; Countryside / Rural; Fur Garments; Gelatin Silver Prints; Hats; Individual Portraits; Makeup; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - A woman sitting in a convertible car facing the trunk. 6.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Photo-Kino Fritz, Berlin, CH-2 (Germany) (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Buildings; Cars; Countryside / Rural; Flags; Gelatin Silver Prints; Germany; Photographic Prints; Women
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - A woman wearing a brooch and hat, seated at a cafe outdoors. 6.2 x 8.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Countryside / Rural; Gelatin Silver Prints; Germany; Hats; Jewellery; Makeup; Photographic Prints; Restaurants; Women
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - A woman at a beach in a white bathing suit putting on her shoe. 6.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - A couple standing on the steps in front of Sanssouci Palace, Potsdam. 8.9 x 6.0 cm, Undated; Photo-Kino Fritz, Berlin, CH-2 (Germany) (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Architecture; Berlin, Germany; Buildings; Couples; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Potsdam, Germany; Studio Photography; Women
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - Hussein Rushdy Beg sitting on the beach with his arms crossed. 6.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Photo-Kino Fritz, Berlin, CH-2 (Germany) (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Bathing Suits / Swimsuits; Beaches; Berlin, Germany; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - Hussein Rushdy Beg and another man standing in front of Sanssouci Palace, Potsdam, Germany. 9.0 x 6.0 cm, Undated; Photo-Kino Fritz, Berlin, CH-2 (Germany) (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Architecture; Berlin, Germany; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Hats; Men; Photographic Prints; Potsdam, Germany; Studio Photography; Suits
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - The 1936 Olympics, view of the stadium. 6.1 x 9.0 cm, August 1936; Photo-Kino Fritz, Berlin, CH-2 (Germany) (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Athletes; Berlin, Germany; Gelatin Silver Prints; Nazis; Olympic Games; Photographic Prints; Sports; Studio Photography
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - The Olympics 1936, view of the stadium. 6.1 x 8.9 cm, August 1936; Photo-Kino Fritz, Berlin, CH-2 (Germany) (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - Three men leaning out the window of a train car, with a conductor standing below them. 8.9 x 6.0 cm, Undated; Photo-Kino Fritz, Berlin, CH-2 (Germany) (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Berlin, Germany; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Suits; Train Station / Railway Station; Trains; Uniforms
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - A male in a striped suit and hat standing view point overlooking the city. 6.5 x 6.2 cm, October 1937; Photo-Kino Fritz, Berlin, CH-2 (Germany) (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Budapest, Hungary; Eye Glasses & Sunglasses; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Suits
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - A woman seated at an outdoor table set for tea/coffee. 6.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Photo-Kino Fritz, Berlin, CH-2 (Germany) (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Berlin, Germany; Drinking; Eating; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Restaurants; Studio Photography; Women
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - Hussein Rushy Beg at a race course with a binocular bag. 6.0 x 6.2 cm, Undated; Photo-Kino Fritz, Berlin, CH-2 (Germany) (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Berlin, Germany; Binoculars; Gelatin Silver Prints; Horse Racing; Horses; Men; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - A woman wearing a hat sitting on the trunk of a convertible. 6.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Photo-Kino Fritz, Berlin, CH-2 (Germany) (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Berlin, Germany; Buildings; Cars; Countryside / Rural; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - A woman sitting in the driver's seat of a convertible. 6.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Photo-Kino Fritz, Berlin, CH-2 (Germany) (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Architecture; Berlin, Germany; Buildings; Cars; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - Hussein Rushdy Beg on the beach. 6.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Bathing Suits / Swimsuits; Beaches; Gelatin Silver Prints; Germany; Men; Photographic Prints
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - Hussein Rushdy Beg and another man standing in a garden. 6.5 x 6.0 cm, October 1937; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Architecture; Budapest, Hungary; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses; Photographic Prints; Statues; Suits
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - A woman sitting on the door of a convertible. 6.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Architecture; Buildings; Cars; Flags; Gelatin Silver Prints; Germany; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Women
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - The 1936 Berlin Olympics, track event, Jesse Owens at the finish line. 6.0 x 8.9 cm, August 1936; Photo-Kino Fritz, Berlin, CH-2 (Germany) (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Athletes; Berlin, Germany; Gelatin Silver Prints; Olympic Games; Photographic Prints; Sports; Studio Photography
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - The 1936 Berlin Olympic Games, with Adolf Hitler in the background. 6.0 x 9.0 cm, August 1936; Photo-Kino Fritz, Berlin, CH-2 (Germany) (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Berlin, Germany; Gelatin Silver Prints; Hitler, Adolf; Nazis; Olympic Games; Photographic Prints; Sports; Studio Photography
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - Hussein Rushdy Beg standing in front of a convertible with his hand in his pocket. 6.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Architecture; Buildings; Cars; Flags; Gelatin Silver Prints; Germany; Individual Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - A woman wearing a hat. English text "To Sap I from Sap II. And all my love. 9.7.37". 12.8 x 8.9 cm, 9 July 1937; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 3)
    English Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Germany; Hats; Individual Portraits; Makeup; Photographic Prints; Women
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - Huseein Rushdy Beg at a table with a woman and man. 8.7 x 12.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Drinking; Eating; Gelatin Silver Prints; Germany; Hats; Men; Photographic Prints; Restaurants; Tea; Women
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - Hussein Rushdy Beg and woman at a formal party. 12.3 x 17.3 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Walter Aber, Berlin=Charl., Bismarckstr. 9, Ruf: Wilh (Germany) (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Berlin, Germany; Bow Ties; Couples; Evening gown / Ball gown; Formal Dress; Fur Garments; Gelatin Silver Prints; Hats; Jewellery; Makeup; Men; Photographic Prints; Restaurants; Studio Photography; Tuxedo; Women
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - Hussein Rushdy Beg and a woman in a photo booth. 5.3 x 3.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Couples; Gelatin Silver Prints; Germany; Jewellery; Makeup; Men; Photo Booth; Photographic Prints; Rings; Women
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - A woman in a white dress sitting on a bench at a race course. 6.0 x 6.1 cm, Undated; Photo-Kino Fritz, Berlin, CH-2 (Germany) (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Berlin, Germany; Gelatin Silver Prints; Horse Racing; Horses; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Sports; Studio Photography; Women
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - Hussein Rushdy Beg sitting at a table drinking with a woman, both wear formal attire. 12.5 x 17.4 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Walter Aber, Berlin=Charl., Bismarckstr. 9, Ruf: Wilh (Germany) (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Alcohol; Berlin, Germany; Bow Ties; Cigarettes; Couples; Formal Dress; Gelatin Silver Prints; Jewellery; Makeup; Photographic Prints; Restaurants; Studio Photography; Tuxedo
  - Hussein Rushdy Beg Series - A newspaper clipping with a picture of Hussein Rushdy Beg. 16.9 x 12.6 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Arabic Writing; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Newspaper Clippings; Photographic Prints; Suits
  - Traditional folk dancing, by a group of young women and men. 9.1 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Studio Photo M. Deroumia, Bab Idriss, Lebanon (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Beirut, Lebanon; Costumes; Dancing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Traditional Dress; Women
  - Europeans in the countryside with a dog sitting in front. "Ingrid" written on the reverse. 8.5 x 13.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Buildings; Countryside / Rural; Dogs; Family; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Houses; Men; Photographic Prints; Unknown Locations; Women
  - A soldier in uniform, with a cigarette and gloves in his hands. Victoria Portrait. 12.5 x 8.2 cm, Undated; Victoria Portrait (Bernhard Wachtl, Wien) (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Cigarettes; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Gloves; Military / Soldiers; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Swords & Knives; Uniforms; Vienna, Austria
  - A group of men and women all wearing a similar hats in a garden/park. English text on reverse talks of "childhood friends". Same writing as ref706. 8.9 x 13.8 cm, 21 May 1895; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Berlin, Germany; English Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Hats; Men; Photographic Prints; Postcards; Uniforms; Women
  - Soldiers in military uniform posing with a sign that reads "Libesgaben werden entgegengenomen". Same handwriting as ref705. 8.9 x 14.0 cm, 21 May 1895; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Berlin, Germany; Cigarettes; English Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; German Writing; Group Portraits; Men; Military / Soldiers; Photographic Prints; Postcards; Signature
  - Two men in suits standing outdoors. French text on reverse: "Souvenir of an excursion to the dams with the University". Same man from ref708. 14.0 x 8.9 cm, 18 March 1938; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Egypt; French Writing; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Signature; Students; Suits
  - Three young men in suits in a garden. French text on reverse: "Souvenir of Thursday, 1 March 1934, passed pleasantly in the garden." Same man from ref706. 8.9 x 14.2 cm, Unknown (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Egypt; French Writing; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Parks; Photographic Prints
  - A couple feeding the pigeons at the Piazza Sr. Marco in Venice. Names written on reverse. 13.9 x 8.8 cm, 1941; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Architecture; Birds; Couples; Gelatin Silver Prints; Hats; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; Venice, Italy; Women
  - A woman leaning on a column in a black dress with a fan. 13.6 x 8.7 cm, Undated; Imperial Photo Studio (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Egypt; Fashion Accessories; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
  - Two men shaking hands in front of a painted backdrop with columns. 13.8 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Suits
  - Two men standing on the steps of a building, one is holding a cigarette. 13.7 x8.6 cm, Undated; A.S. Milionis, Alexandria (Egypt) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Alexandria, Egypt; Cigarettes; Fezes / Tarbouches; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Uniforms
  - An elderly woman looking off camera wearing a dark coat. 14.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Coats; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
  - A young female in a white dress with a large white bow in her hair and one male in a short suit. 14.0 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Studio Nicolas Pappazoglou, Le Caire, Egypte (Cairo, Egypt) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Boys; Cairo, Egypt; Clocks & Watches; Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Jewellery; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
  - A man in a suit looking off camera. 13.5 x 8.4 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - A man, woman and three children posing for a family portrait. 13.7 x 8.6 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Boys; Children; Egypt; Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Medals; Men; Photographic Prints; Religious Crosses; Studio Photography; Women
  - A cropped portrait of a young man wearing a suit and a tie-pin. 13.9 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints; Suits
  - Two buses with the same logo in front of some large buildings. 8.1 x 13.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Buses; Costumes; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints
  - A young man in a Christian religious outfit holding a book with a cross on it. 14.0 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Christians; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Religious Clothing; Religious Crosses; Studio Photography; Traditional Dress
  - A multi-generational group in a studio portrait. 8.8 x 13.8 cm, Undated; Studio Hanein (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Bow Ties; Canes/Walking Sticks; Egypt; Family Portraits; Fezes / Tarbouches; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Men; Military / Soldiers; Mustaches; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Uniforms; Women